Washington Area Performing Arts Video Archives (WAPAVA)
DC Public Library Special Collections
- Series 1
  - Henry VIII - Folger Theatre, 2010-11-13 - 2010-11-13 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Leading Ladies - Ford’s Theatre, 2005-10-21 - 2005-10-21 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Mrs. Farnsworth - Rep Stage, 2007-09-23 - 2007-09-23 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Opus - Washington Stage Guild, 2007-09-29 - 2007-09-29 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Pillowman - Studio Theatre, 2007-04-08 - 2007-04-08 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Sabrina Fair - Ford’s Theatre, 2010-10-01 - 2010-10-24 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Seagull, The - Stage Rep, 2004-09-24 - 2004-10-10 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Story of Christmas Glimpses of the Moon - Metro Stage, 2010-09-10 - 2010-10-17 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Tintypes - Stage Rep, 2006-10-27 - 2006-11-19 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Witches of Eastwick - Signature Theatre, 2007-07-14 - 2007-07-14 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Back at Leipzig - Rep Stage, 2007-03-25 - 2007-03-25 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Blues for an Alabama Sky - African Continuum Theatre Company, 2011-05-08 - 2011-05-08 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Boston Marriage - Actor’s Theatre of Washington, 2006-03-26 - 2006-03-26 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Children’s Hour, The - Rep Stage, 2005-03-12 - 2005-03-12 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Evita - Open Circle Theatre, 2007-07-14 - 2007-07-14 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Fanny’s First Play - Washington Stage Guild, 2006-04-01 - 2006-04-01 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Glass Menagerie, The - Rep Stage, 2010-01-25 - 2010-01-25 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Hysteria - Rep Stage, 2009-10-29 - 2009-10-29 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Intimate Apparel - African Continuum Theatre, 2008-05-17 - 2008-05-17 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Kimberly Akimbo - Rep Stage, 2005-02-20 - 2005-02-20 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Liberty Smith - Ford's Theatre, 2011-04-02 - 2011-04-02 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Road to Mecca, The - Studio Theatre, 2008-10-04 - 2008-10-04 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Stones in his Pocket - Rep Stage, 2006-10-08 - 2006-10-08 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Take me Out - Studio Theatre, 2005-08-24 - 2005-08-24 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Two by Pinter - Rep Stage, 2007-02-25 - 2007-02-25 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Two Trains Running - African Continuum Theatre Company, 2004-11-27 - 2004-11-27 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - 2011 Helen Hayes Awards - Warner Theatre, 2011-04-25 - 2011-04-25 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Bobrauchenbergameria - Forum Theatre, 2011-06-25 - 2011-06-25 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Candide - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2011-01-08 - 2011-01-08 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Chesapeake - Bay Theatre Company, 2011-05-15 - 2011-05-15 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Dybbuk, The - Theatre J/Synetic Theatre, 2006-03-19 - 2006-03-19 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Follies - JFK Center for the Performing Arts, 2011-05-28 - 2011-05-28 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Glass Menagerie, The - Georgetown University/Arena Stage, 2011-07-02 - 2011-07-02 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Green Bird, The - Constellation Theatre, 2011-05-28 - 2011-05-28 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Ideal Husband, An - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2011-04-07 - 2011-04-07 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - La Candida Erendira - Gala Hispanic Theatre, 2011-02-26 - 2011-02-26 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Mascows of Nantucket, The - Theatre J, 2011-06-05 - 2011-06-05 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Night and Day - The Washington Shakespeare Company, 2011-07-15 - 2011-07-15 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Opus - Washington Stage Guild Theatre, 2007-09-26 - 2007-09-26 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Rosenarants and Guildenstern are Dead - Studio Theatre, 2007-06-30 - 2007-06-30 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Squrriel, or the Orgin of a Species - A Production of the Capital Fringe Theatre, 2011-07-15 - 2011-07-15 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Venus in Fur - Studio Theatre, 2011-07-09 - 2011-07-09 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Beertown - Dog and Pony DC Theatre, 2011-12-10 - 2011-12-10 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Carol: A Ghost Story of Christmas - Ford’s Theatre, 2011-12-10 - 2011-12-10 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Habit of Art, The - Studio Theatre, 2011-10-22 - 2011-10-22 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Happy Days - WRC Awant Bard Theatre, 2011-09-17 - 2011-09-17 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Heir Apparent, The - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2011-10-08 - 2011-10-08 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Imagining Madoff - Theatre J, 2011-09-25 - 2011-09-25 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Lithuanian - Artisphere, Arlington, VA Theatre, 2011-10-02 - 2011-10-02 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Love Cures Cancer - Artisphere, Arlington, VA Theatre, 2011-09-25 - 2011-09-25 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Manifesto! - A Capital Fringe Production Theatre, 2011-07-20 - 2011-07-20 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Merchant of Venice, The - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2011-07-09 - 2011-07-09 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Notes to the Motherland - Artisphere, Arlington, VA Theatre, 2011-09-18 - 2011-09-18 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Old Times - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2011-06-04 - 2011-06-04 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Othello - Folger Theatre, 2011-11-16 - 2011-11-16 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Parade - Ford’s Theatre Society, 2011-10-15 - 2011-10-15 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Shayna Maidel, A - Rep Stage Theatre, 2007-11-03 - 2007-11-03 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Who’s Your Baghdaddy? - The New Music Foundation and The…, 2011-07-15 - 2011-07-15 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Wilder Sins - Washington Stage Guild Theatre, 2011-11-26 - 2011-11-26 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - 1776 - Ford’s Theatre Society, 2012-03-24 - 2012-03-24 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Ameilia - Washington Stage Guild, 2012-02-11 - 2012-02-11 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Belle of Amherst, The - Bay Theatre Company, 2012-05-06 - 2012-05-06 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Gaming Table, The - Folger Theatre Company, 2012-03-03 - 2012-03-03 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - James Joyce's The Dead - University of Maryland, 2009-10-24 - 2009-10-24 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Maryland Dance Ensemble Spring 2011 - University of Maryland, 2011-04-16 - 2011-04-16 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - On the Waterfront - American Century Theatre, 2012-04-28 - 2012-04-28 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Oxygen - Taffety Punk Theatre Company, 2012-05-17 - 2012-05-17 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Side Man - First Stage Theatre, 2012-04-21 - 2012-04-21 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Spring 2012 Shared MFA Thesis Concert - University of Maryland, 2012-03-09 - 2012-03-09 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Strange Interlude - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2012-04-20 - 2012-04-20 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Superheroes Celebrity Rehab The Musical - Capital Fringe Festival, 2012, 2012-07-22 - 2012-07-22 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Trumbo - Rep Stage Theatre, 2008-09-25 - 2008-09-25 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Yellowman - Rep Stage Theatre, 2012-02-23 - 2012-02-23 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Beauty Queen of Lenane, The - Keegan Theatre, 2005-07-10 - 2005-07-10 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Butterfinger’s Angel, The - Rep Stage, 2009-01-04 - 2009-01-04 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Dracula - Synetic Theatre, 2005-10-16 - 2005-10-16 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Dreams in the Arms of the Binding Lady - Capital Fringe Festival, 2012, 2012-06-23 - 2012-06-23 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Everything in the Garden - University of Maryland, 2012-03-10 - 2012-03-10 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Intelligence - Rep Stage, 2008-11-06 - 2008-11-06 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Long Day’s Journey into Night - Arena Stage Theatre, 2012-05-05 - 2012-05-05 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Merry Wives of Windsor, The - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2012-07-07 - 2012-07-07 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Mrs. Warren’s Profession - Rep Stage, 2008-02-02 - 2008-02-02 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Much Ado About Nothing - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2011-12-29 - 2011-12-29 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Necessary Sacrifices, The - Ford’s Theatre Company, 2012-02-11 - 2012-02-11 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Sandwalk - University of Maryland, 2012-04-29 - 2012-04-29 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Servant of 2 Masters, The - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2012-05-19 - 2012-05-19 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Taming of the Shrew - Folger Theatre, 2012-05-26 - 2012-05-26 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Two Gentlemen of Verona, The - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2012-02-25 - 2012-02-25 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - 2012 Helen Hayes Awards - Warner Theatre, 2012-04-23 - 2012-04-23 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Am I Black Enough Yet? - University of Maryland, 2010-11-13 - 2010-11-13 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Anna in the Tropics - University of Maryland, 2009-11-07 - 2009-11-07 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Bluest Eye, The - University of Maryland, 2012-02-18 - 2012-02-18 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Child Should Lead Them, A - University of Maryland, 2011-11-13 - 2011-11-13 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Dreams in the Arms of the Binding Lady - Capital Fringe Festival, 2012, 2012-06-23 - 2012-06-23 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Enchanted April - University of Maryland, 2012-02-18 - 2012-02-18 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Gilgamesh - University of Maryland, 2010-05-01 - 2010-05-01 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Old Settler, The - University of Maryland, 2012-02-18 - 2012-02-18 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Religion Thing, The - Theatre J, 2012-01-22 - 2012-01-22 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Seagull, The - University of Maryland, 2011-03-05 - 2011-03-05 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Welcome Home Jenny Slutter - University of Maryland, 2011-02-19 - 2011-02-19 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Celebration of the Life of Jaylee M. Mead, A -, 2012-10-18 - 2012-10-18 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Carol: A Ghost Story of Christmas - Ford’s Theatre, 2012-12-08 - 2012-12-08 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Conference of the Birds, The - Folger Theatre, 2011-04-28 - 2011-04-28 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Cyrano - Folger Theatre, 2011-04-28 - 2011-04-28 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Dante’s Inferno - Washington Stage Guild Theatre, 2013-03-26 - 2013-03-26 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Ghost-Writer - Metro Stage, 2013-05-11 - 2013-05-11 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Government Inspector, The - Shakespeare Theater Company, 2013-10-25 - 2013-10-25 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Hello, Dolly! - Ford’s Theatre, 2013-03-23 - 2013-03-23 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Cassiopeia - University of Maryland, 2010-02-18 - 2010-02-18 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - How to Write a New Book for the Bible - Round House Theatre, 2013-05-04 - 2013-05-04 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Hughie - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2013-03-08 - 2013-03-08 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Killing Game, A - Dog B Pony DC, 2012-12-20 - 2012-12-20 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Maryland Dance Ensemble Counter-Point - University of Maryland, 2010-12-04 - 2010-12-04 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Maryland Dance Ensemble Fall 2009 - University of Maryland, 2009-12-05 - 2009-12-05 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Minotaur - University of Maryland, 2011-04-23 - 2011-04-23 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Creative Soles Blossoming: Spring 2012 - University of Maryland, 2012-04-22 - 2012-04-22 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Fly - Ford’s Theatre Society, 2013-09-28 - 2013-09-28 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to Forum - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2014-01-14 - 2014-01-14 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Henry V - Folger Theatre, 2013-02-16 - 2013-02-16 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - James Joyce’s “The Dead” - Quotidian Theatre, 2012-12-07 - 2012-12-07 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Maryland Dance Ensemble Shared Graduate - University of Maryland, 2012-02-17 - 2012-02-17 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Scapin - Consellation Theatre Company, 2014-02-18 - 2014-02-18 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Shared MFA Thesis Concert - University of Maryland, 2011-10-21 - 2011-10-21 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Show-Off, The - American Century Theatre, 2013-02-02 - 2013-02-02 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - 36 Views Act 1 and Act 2 - Constellation Theater Company, 2013-11-17 - 2013-11-17 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Apple Family Plays: Sweet and Sad - Studio Theatre, 2014-02-21 - 2014-02-21 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Apple Family Plays: That Hopey Changey… - Studio Theatre, 2014-02-20 - 2014-02-20 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Cab Colloway’s Minnie the Moocher - Pointless Theatre, 2014-03-02 - 2014-03-02 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Christmas Carol: A Ghost Story of Christmas - Ford’s Theatre Company, 2013-12-14 - 2013-12-14 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - King John Act I and II - WSC Arant Bard, 2013-11-11 - 2013-11-11 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Lyle the Crocodile - Imagination Stage, 2013-12-19 - 2013-12-19 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Matchmaker Act I and II - University of Maryland, 2013-10-19 - 2013-10-19 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Moliere Impromptu Act I and II - University of Maryland, 2013-11-10 - 2013-11-10 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Our Suburb Act I and II - Theater J, 2014-01-11 - 2014-01-11 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Seminar - Round House Theatre, 2014-03-02 - 2014-03-02 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Torch Song Trilogy Act I, II, and III - Studio Theatre, 2013-10-12 - 2013-10-12 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Violet Act I and II - Ford’s Theatre Society, 2014-02-08 - 2014-02-08 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - All’s Well That Ends Well Act I and II - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2010-10-30 - 2010-10-30 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Coriolanus Act I and II - Shakespeare Theater Company, 2013-06-01 - 2013-06-01 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Edgar and Annabel - Studio Theatre/2nd Stage, 2014-01-02 - 2014-01-02 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Laramie Project, The Act I, II, and III - Ford’s Theater Company, 2013-10-26 - 2013-10-26 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Late: A Cowboy Song - No Rules Theatre Company, 2014-01-19 - 2014-01-19 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Lulu and the Brontosaurus - Imagination Stage, 2013-10-03 - 2013-10-03 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Measure for Measure Act I and II - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2013-09-21 - 2013-09-21 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Midsummer Night’s Dream, A Act I and II - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2012-12-18 - 2012-12-18 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Moth - Studio Theatre, 2014-05-04 - 2014-05-04 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Optimism! Or Voltaire’s Candide Act I and II - Spooky Action Theater, 2013-05-12 - 2013-05-12 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Twelfth Night Act I and II - Folger Theater, 2013-05-25 - 2013-05-25 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Two Character Play, The Act I and II - Spooky Action Theatre, 2013-10-13 - 2013-10-13 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Winter’s Tale, The Act I and II - Shakespeare Theater Company, 2011-06-19 - 2011-06-19 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Amadeus Act I and II - Round House Theatre, 2011-06-11 - 2011-06-11 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Becky Shaw Act I and II - Round House Theatre, 2013-05-22 - 2013-05-22 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Elder Statesman, The Act I, II, III - Washington Stage Guild, 2013-05-18 - 2013-05-18 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Gentlemen of Verona, The Act II - Folger Theatre, 2004-12-11 - 2004-12-11 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Henry IV, Part 1 - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2014-04-12 - 2014-04-12 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Henry IV, Part 2 - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2014-04-19 - 2014-04-19 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Henry VIII - Folger Theatre, 2010-11-13 - 2010-11-13 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Importance of Being Earnest, The - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2014-03-01 - 2014-03-01 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Last Days of Judas Iscariot, The Act I - Forum Theatre, 2008-04-26 - 2008-04-26 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - On the Verge Act I and II - Rep Stage, 2010-04-29 - 2010-04-29 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Our Town Act I, II, III - Ford’s Theatre, 2013-02-02 - 2013-02-02 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Romeo and Juliet - Synetic Theatre, 2008-03-06 - 2008-03-06 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Romeo and Juliet Act I and II - Folger Theatre, 2013-11-27 - 2013-11-27 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Salome - Scena Theatre, 2013-10-17 - 2013-10-17 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Tribes - Studio Theatre, 2014-01-23 - 2014-01-23 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Twelfth Night Act I and II - Taffety Punk Theatre Company, 2013-02-16 - 2013-02-16 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Two Gentlemen of Verona - Folger Theatre, 2004-12-11 - 2004-12-11 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Two Trains Running - Round House Theatre, 2014-03-03 - 2014-03-03 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Wallenstein Act I and II - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2013-05-31 - 2013-05-31 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Winter’s Tale, The Act I and II - Folger Theatre, 2009-02-21 - 2009-02-21 (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - 28th Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee - Ford's Theatre, 2012-03-29 - 2012-03-29 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream - University of Maryland, 2012-09-29 - 2012-09-29 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Admission, The - Busboys and Poets/Theatre J, 2014-05-17 - 2014-05-17 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Back to Methuselah - Washington Stage Guild, 2014-03-22 - 2014-03-22 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Breathe, Rhythm, Flight - University of Maryland, 2012-12-01 - 2012-12-01 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Rent - University of Maryland, 2013-02-22 - 2013-02-22 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Richard III - Folger Theatre, 2014-03-25 - 2014-03-25 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Shared Dance MFA Thesis Concert parts I and II - University of Maryland, 2012-10-19 - 2012-10-19 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Shared Graduate Dance Concert - University of Maryland, 2013-02-22 - 2013-02-22 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Spring Awakening - University of Maryland, 2014-03-08 - 2014-03-08 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Waiting Room, The - University of Maryland, 2014-02-22 - 2014-02-22 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Water by the Spoonful - Studio Theatre, 2014-03-12 - 2014-03-12 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Wedding Dress - Spooky Action Theatre, 2014-02-23 - 2014-02-23 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - An onstage conversation with Edward Albee - Georgetown University, 2009-05-03 - 2009-05-03 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Apple Falling - University of Maryland, 2013-03-15 - 2013-03-15 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Breathe, Rhythm, Flight - University of Maryland, 2012-02-01 - 2012-02-01 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Cinderella: The Remix - Imagination Stage, 2014-03-05 - 2014-03-05 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Comedy of Errors - Folger Theatre, 2011-02-06 - 2011-02-06 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Dead Man's Cell Phone - University of Maryland, 2013-03-09 - 2013-03-09 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - In the Red and Brown Water - University of Maryland, 2012-11-10 - 2012-11-13 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - In the Time of Roses - University of Maryland, 2013-05-04 - 2013-05-04 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Rumpelstiltskin - Imagination Stage, 2014-05-04 - 2014-05-04 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Souvenir - Studio Theatre, 2007-07-14 - 2007-07-14 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Springing from Fantasy - University of Maryland, 2013-02-21 - 2013-04-02 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Twilight Los Angeles: 1992 - University of Maryland, 2014-07-04 - 2014-07-04 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - 101 Dalmations - Imagination Stage, 2015-01-09 - 2015-01-09 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Back to Methuselah - Washington Stage Guild, 2015-03-07 - 2015-03-07 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Blue Door - African Continuum Theatre, 2009-05-03 - 2009-05-03 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Carrie: The Musical - Studio 2nd Stage, 2014-06-23 - 2014-06-23 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Cock - Studio Theatre, 2014-06-13 - 2014-06-13 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Cook - Studio Theatre, 2014-06-13 - 2014-06-13 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Freud's Last Session - Theatre J, 2014-06-22 - 2014-06-22 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Happy Days - Scena Theatre, 2014-06-05 - 2014-06-05 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Kwaidan - Spooky Action Theatre, 2014-06-19 - 2014-06-19 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Last of the Whyos - Spooky Action Theatre, 2015-02-22 - 2015-02-22 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - On the Razzle - Constellation Theatre Company, 2011-02-26 - 2011-02-26 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Private Lives - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2014-06-28 - 2014-06-28 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Rock 'n' Roll - Studio Theatre, 2009-05-24 - 2009-05-24 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Stupid Fucking Bird - Woolly Mammoth Theatre Company, 2014-08-13 - 2014-08-13 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - The Musical - Studio 2nd Stage, 2014-06-13 - 2014-06-13 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Two Gentlemen of Verona - Folger Theatre/Fiasco Theatre, 2014-05-24 - 2014-05-24 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Collidescope - University of Maryland, 2014-11-08 - 2014-11-08 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Dontrell, Who Kissed the Sea - Theatre Alliance, 2015-05-30 - 2015-05-30 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Fiddler on the Roof - Arena Stage, 2014-12-07 - 2014-12-07 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Freedom's Song: Abraham Lincoln and the Civil War - Ford's Theatre, 2014-04-08 - 2014-04-08 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Good Kids - University of Maryland, 2015-03-01 - 2015-03-01 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Julius Caesar - Folger Theatre, 2014-12-06 - 2014-12-06 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Letters - Metro Stage, 2015-06-14 - 2015-06-14 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Lost World - University of Maryland, 2015-02-22 - 2015-02-22 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Mary Stuart - Folger Theatre, 2015-03-07 - 2015-03-07 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Metromaniacs - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2015-02-11 - 2015-02-11 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Night Fairy - Imagination Stage, 2014-10-24 - 2014-10-24 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Old Wicked Songs - 1st Stage, 2015-05-10 - 2015-05-10 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Rosencrantz and Guildernstern are Dead - Folger Theatre, 2015-03-07 - 2015-03-07 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Shipment - Forum Theatre, 2015-06-13 - 2015-06-13 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - The Veil - Quotidian Theatre Company, 2014-08-09 - 2014-08-09 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Turn of the Screw - Creative Cauldron, 2015-02-21 - 2015-02-21 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Wiley and the Hairy Man - Imagination Stage, 1900-01-00 - 1900-01-00 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - 110 In The Shade - Ford's Theatre, 2016-03-26 - 2016-03-26 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - A Christmas Carol - A Ghost Story of Christmas - Ford's Theatre, 2015-12-12 - 2015-12-12 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - BFG - Imagination Stage, 2014-07-23 - 2014-07-23 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Glass Menagerie - Ford's Theatre, 2016-01-30 - 2016-01-30 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Human Capacity - University of Maryland, 2015-05-03 - 2015-05-03 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - It's a Wonderful Life - Stage Guild, 2015-11-28 - 2015-11-28 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Man of La Mancha - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2015-04-11 - 2015-04-11 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Maytag Virgin - Quotidian Theatre Company, 2015-10-24 - 2015-10-24 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream - Folger Theatre, 2016-02-10 - 2016-02-10 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Old Wicked Songs - 1st Stage, 2015-05-10 - 2015-05-10 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Pericles - Folger Theatre, 2015-11-25 - 2015-11-25 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Salome - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2015-10-23 - 2015-10-23 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Tartuffe - University of Maryland, 2015-11-08 - 2015-11-08 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Venus in Fur - Rep Stage, 2014-10-16 - 2014-10-16 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Whale - Rep Stage, 2015-01-29 - 2015-01-29 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - An Almost Holy Picture - Rep Stage, 2010-09-09 - 2010-09-09 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Circle Mirror Transformation - Rep Stage, 2015-06-25 - 2015-06-25 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Entertaining Mr Sloane - Edge of the Universe Players 2, 2015-12-12 - 2015-12-12 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - God's Ear - Rep Stage, 2009-04-23 - 2009-04-23 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Kiss Me, Kate - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2015-12-19 - 2015-12-19 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Othello - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 1900-01-00 - 1900-01-00 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Piano Teacher - Rep Stage, 2014-02-20 - 2014-02-20 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Sinbad: The Untold Tale - Imagination Stage, 2015-05-01 - 2015-05-01 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Sisters Rosenweig - Theatre J, 2016-01-22 - 2016-01-22 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Sons of the Prophet - Theatre J, 2015-12-02 - 2015-12-02 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Speech and Debate - Rep Stage, 2011-04-28 - 2011-04-28 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Stars of David - Theatre J, 2015-12-26 - 2015-12-26 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Sunset Baby - Rep Stage, 2015-05-07 - 2015-05-07 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - T Party - Forum Theatre, 2015-01-17 - 2015-01-17 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Temperamentals - Rep Stage, 2012-09-05 - 2012-09-05 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Two by J.M. Barrie - Rep Stage, 2010-10-21 - 2010-10-21 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Widow Lincoln - Ford's Theatre, 2015-01-31 - 2015-01-31 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - A Lie of the Mind - Rep Stage, 2009-02-26 - 2009-02-26 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Boeing Boeing - Rep Stage, 2013-05-02 - 2016-06-25 (Box 106, Folder 2)